Citizens Budget Commission Records apap201
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Citizens Budget Commission Records
1931-1999
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Citizens Budget Commission, New York
apap201
12.92 cubic ft.
The Citizens Budget Commission contain information on the financial outlook of New York City from the 1930's to the 1990's.
Box 1
Box 2
Box 3
Box 4
Box 5
Box 6
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department Special Collections and Archives, by the Citizens Budget Commission in August 2005.
Administrative History
The Citizens Budget Commission (CBC) is a nonpartisan, nonprofit civic organization devoted to influencing constructive change in the finances and services of New York City and New York State government.[Citizens Budget Commission: About the Citizens Budget Commission, http://www.cbcny.org/about.html Accessed July 18, 2006] The inspiration for the group was New York City's inability to manage its budget. The CBC took on the responsibility of analyzing and evaluating New York City's finances. This information was used to create recommendations and reports designed to help New York City. This responsibility was expanded from New York City to state government in 1984. The CBC believes that the interests of the citizenry of New York is of foremost importance and should guide their actions and responses.[ "A Profile of the Citizens Budget Commission," Series 6, Box 1, Folder 21, 1995.]
The CBC was founded in 1932 during the Great Depression when Jimmy Walker was mayor of New York City. When Fiorello LaGuardia became mayor in 1934, New York City, like the rest of the nation, was in a poor financial position. LaGuardia worked to resolve New York City's financial problems. The CBC offered criticism and advice throughout this period, which is documented in the news clippings in the collection. The CBC conducted research and released reports meant to be unbiased based on the needs of the people and intended to be what was best for New York City. Out of this time of financial struggle grew the Citizens Budget Commission. Another financial crisis in New York City's history occurred in the mid-1970s. A combination of generous welfare spending in the 1960s and a stock market decline in the 1970s put New York City in financial peril. One example of advice the CBC gave New York City during this time was to urge the city to provide only essential services and even at that level to do it economically.["Citizens Budget Commission Urges City Provide Only Essential Services, Phase Out 'Pernicious' Practice of Borrowing for Recurring Expenses," Series 7, Box 6, Folder 1, April 14, 1975.]
For over seventy years the CBC has acted as the financial voice of reason for New York City and more recently for all of New York State. CBC's changing responsibility to include all of New York State is explained in their 1984 annual report. The CBC became concerned when state government violated rules of state and local finance in their budget practices.[ "Annual Report: 1984," Series 3, Box 1, Folder 16.] The most recent annual report in the records from 1992 reports on a committee the CBC created to research the connection between the City of New York and the rest of the state on fiscal responsibility. Some of the results revealed that New York City is the source of about one-third of the entire state's revenues while 20% of New York City's revenues are received through state aid. This committee was designed to help solve the "finger pointing" dilemma that statistics such as these caused between New York City and New York State.["60th Anniversary Report: 1932-1992," Series 3, Box 1, Folder 17.]
Today the CBC is led by a president who oversees a research and administrative staff. The board of trustees are under the guidance of a ruling chair. The CBC's current function is nearly identical to its purpose in 1932 when it was first created-convincing New York to act wisely with its money.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Citizens Budget Commission (CBC) contain information on the financial outlook of New York City from the 1930s to the 1990s. The majority of information in the records contains research, statistics, updates, suggestions, and summaries of New York City's financial standing.
Administrative information is available in the form of minutes, photographs, and personal information about members of the board of trustees. The meeting minutes of the CBC for the board of trustees and its members end in 1973. Publications date from 1931-1999. The bulk of the records are from the reports and releases series. Some of the releases correlate to the reports with exact dates for each series capable of being found and compared through the chronological order they were filed in.
Related Collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guides for Social Activists and Public Advocates and Public Servants and Politicians.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Public Servants; Business and Industry; New York (State). Budget, Division of the; Citizens Budget Commission (New York, N.Y.); Financial planners; New York (State); Annual reports; Newspaper clippings; Administrative records; Reports; Minutes; Releases (discharges); Financial Records; Photographs; Citizens Budget Commission (New York, N.Y.)
- Administrative Files, 1932-1973; 1978; 1994-1995; Undated; 1; 1.53 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged by topic.
  Scope and Contents
  The bulk of the series is the Citizens Budget Commission's (CBC) minutes from 1932 through 1973. These include minutes from the executive sessions of the board of trustees, adjourned meetings of the board of trustees and the nominating committee, and the minutes of the annual meetings of members of the CBC. In 1978, the biographies of the trustees of CBC were compiled and photographs of many of these individuals are included. The series is arranged by topic with the minutes in chronological order.
  - Biographies, List of Trustees, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Biographies of Trustees, B-K, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Biographies of Trustees, L-R, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Biographies of Trustees, S-W, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Information on New York City's Past Budget, 1994; 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - President's Report, 1973 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Unreleased CBC Studies, 1968-1973 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1932 July-1933 September (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1933 September-1936 September (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Minutes, December 1936-December 1940 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Minutes, December 1940-December 1945 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Minutes, March 1946-September 1952 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1952 November-1957 May (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Minutes, September 1957-February 1959 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1959 February-1961 March (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1961 April-1965 December (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1966 February-1967 December (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1968 January-1968 December (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Minutes, 1969 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - By-laws, 1943; 1958; 1968-1972; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1932; 1938; 1946; 1966-1969; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
- Annual Dinner, 1952-1984; 1993; 2; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  The Citizens Budget Commission has held an annual dinner since 1932. The annual dinner celebrates influential individuals. This series contains dinner programs and invitations. Many of the programs have pictures of the honorees. In 1993, a speech was given at the annual dinner by Vincent Tese, who at the time was the director of economic development for New York State. The written version of this speech is in this series.
  - Golden Anniversary Packets, 1982 (Box 1 (2- Annual Dinner), Folder 1)
  - Programs and Invitations, 1952-1978 (Box 1 (2- Annual Dinner), Folder 2)
  - Programs and Invitations, 1976-1983 (Box 1 (2- Annual Dinner), Folder 3)
  - Programs and Invitations, 1979-1984 (Box 1 (2- Annual Dinner), Folder 4)
  - Speech by Vincent Tese, 1993 (Box 1 (2- Annual Dinner), Folder 5)
- Annual Reports, 1934-1988; 1992; 3; 1 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  The Citizens Budget Commission issues an annual report updating the fiscal status of New York City. These reports list the officers and trustees of the CBC and highlights from the previous year.
  - Annual Reports, 1934-1939 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1940-1944 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1945-1947 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1987-1988; 1992 (Box 1 (3-Annual Reports), Folder 17)
- News Clippings, 1934-1941; 1968-1974; 1979-1982; 4; 0.9 cubic ft.
  An oversized, bound book of news clippings holds content about New York City's financial struggles from 1934-1941. Many of the articles contain information about Fiorello LaGuardia, Mayor of New York City from 1934-1945. The news clippings are from New York City newspapers such as the New York Times and the Long Island Press. There are both photocopied and original news clippings. Many of the news clippings from the 1960s and 1970s are about Mayor John Lindsay and his efforts to fix New York City's budget problems.
  - Citizens Budget Commission News Clippings, Bound Volume, 1934 January-1941 April (Box 1 (4-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1968 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1969 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1970 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1971 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1972 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1973 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1974 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings), Folder 3)
- Photographs, 1978-1982; 1988; Undated; 5; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically by photograph size.
  The photographs are primarily of the CBC's annual dinners between 1978 and 1982. Most of the photographs are 8 x 10 inches in size with one folder containing 5 x 7 inch photographs. Photographs of the 1982 50th anniversary dinner are in the box as well.
  - Annual Dinner, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Annual Dinner, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Annual Dinner, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Annual Dinner, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Annual Dinner, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Annual Dinner, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Annual Dinner, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinner, 5 x 7 and Negatives, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Annual Dinner, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - 50th Anniversary Annual Dinner and Activities, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Annual Dinner, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Negatives, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Mayor Ed Koch and others, Undated (Box 1 (5-Photographs), Folder 13)
- Publications, 1931-1999; 6; 1.33 cubic ft.
  The publications all deal with New York City and its financial status. Some of the material in this series is in report form, but is not included in the reports series because it is bound. Included in the publications are a series of pocket summaries (small pocket sized cards) that summarize New York City's finances year by year. The CBC Quarterly, a CBC newsletter publication, has nearly its entire run included in the series, with only a couple issues missing.
  - "Change at 61st Street!,", 1966 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
  - "City Taxes: A Handbook,", 1936 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
  - "City Traffic Control,", 1948 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
  - "Civil Service in the City of New York,", 1938 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
  - "Compensation, Conditions of Employment and Retirement Benefits of Policemen and Firemen,", 1938 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
  - "The Cost of the Administration of County Government in the City of New York," Original Copy, 1934 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
  - "The Cost of the Administration of County Government in the City of New York," Revised Copy, 1934 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
  - "The Cost of the Administration of the Courts in the City of New York,", 1933 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
  - "Financial Aspects of New York City's Pension Systems,", 1933 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
  - "Fiscal Facts Concerning the City of New York,", 1940 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
  - "Fiscal Facts Concerning the City of New York," Vol.2, 1947 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
  - "For Better Personal Administration in the City of New York,", 1946 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
  - "The General Business and Financial Tax in New York City,", 1963 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
  - "Judiciary Report,", 1935 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
  - "New York City's Debt History,", 1931 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
  - "New York City's Deputy Mayor City Administrator,", 1966 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
  - "Pension Report,", 1933 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
  - "Pertinent Facts,", 1932 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
  - "Pocket Summaries of New York City Finances,", 1972; 1975-1979; 1982-1984; 1987; 1991-1999 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 19)
  - "Police Department: Investigation of Hack Bureau,", 1933 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Profile and Study of the Citizens Budget Commission, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 21)
  - "The Record of Transit Fares in 39 American Cities,", 1943 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 22)
  - "Report on the Master Plan of Land Use,", 1941 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 23)
  - "Should NYC Adopt Fiscal Independence for Education,", 1950 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 24)
  - "Transit Primer,", 1934 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 25)
  - CBC Quarterly, 1981-1983 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
  - CBC Quarterly, 1984-1986 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
  - CBC Quarterly, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
  - CBC Quarterly, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
  - CBC Quarterly"The Watchdog,", 1994 (Box 2 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
- Releases, 1932-1999; 7; 5.5 cubic ft.
  Some of the releases are linked to the reports in Series 8, but due to their varying nature and bulk, have been separated. Releases include memorandums, transit information, statements, notices, information on reports that were released simultaneously, and information on a wide range of other topics related to New York City's financial situation from the 1930s through 1990s, and on all of New York State from 1984 to the 1990s.
  - Releases, 1932 June-1932 September (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, 1932 October-1932 December (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1933 January-1933 February (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, 1933 March-1933 May (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, 1933 June-1933 September (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, October 1933-December 1933 (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1934 January-1934 June (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, July 1934-December 1934 (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1935 January-1935 April (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, May 1935-December 1935 (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1936 January-1936 June (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1936 July-1936 December (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1937 (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 13)
  - Releases, 1938 (Box 1 (7-Releases), Folder 14)
  - Releases, 1939 January-1939 April (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, May 1939-December 1939 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, January 1940-April 1940 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, 1940 May-1940 December (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, 1941 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1942 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1943 January-1943 May (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1943 June-1943 December (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1944 January-1944 May (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, 1944 June-1944 December (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1945 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1946 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1947 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 13)
  - Releases, 1948 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 14)
  - Releases, 1949 (Box 2 (7-Releases), Folder 15)
  - Releases, 1950 January-1950 March (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, 1950 April-1950 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1951 January-1951 May (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, 1951 June-1951 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, 1952 January-1952 April (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1952 May-1952 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1953 January-1953 April (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1953 May-1953 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1954 January-1954 May (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, 1954 June-1954 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1955 January-1955 May (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1955 June-1955 December (Box 3 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1956 January-1956 June (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, 1956 July-1956 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1957 January-1957 May (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, 1957 June-1957 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, January 1958-June 1958 (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1958 July-1958 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1959 January-1959 April (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1959 May-1959 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1960 January-1960 March (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, 1960 April-1960 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1961 (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1962 January-1962 April (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1962 May-1962 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 13)
  - Releases, 1963 January-1963 July (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 14)
  - Releases, 1963 August-1963 December (Box 4 (7-Releases), Folder 15)
  - Releases, 1964 January-1964 May (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, 1964 June-1964 December (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1965 January-1965 June (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, July 1965-December 1965 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, 1966 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1967 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1968 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1969 January-1969 May (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1969 June-1969 December (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, 1970 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1971 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1972 January-1972 May (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1972 June-1972 December (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 13)
  - Releases, 1973 January-1973 June (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 14)
  - Releases, 1973 July-1973 December (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 15)
  - Releases, January 1974-May 1974 (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 16)
  - Releases, 1974 June-1974 December (Box 5 (7-Releases), Folder 17)
  - Releases, 1975 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 1)
  - Releases, 1976 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 2)
  - Releases, 1977 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 3)
  - Releases, 1978 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 4)
  - Releases, 1979 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 5)
  - Releases, 1980 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 6)
  - Releases, 1981 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 8)
  - Releases, 50th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 9)
  - Releases, 1983 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 10)
  - Releases, 1984 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 11)
  - Releases, 1985-1987 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 12)
  - Releases, 1988-1990 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 13)
  - Releases, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 14)
  - Releases, 1993 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 15)
  - Releases, 1994 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 16)
  - Releases, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 17)
  - Releases, 1997 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 18)
  - Releases, 1998 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 19)
  - Releases, 1999 (Box 6 (7-Releases), Folder 20)
- Reports, 1931-1999; 8; 2 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically
  The main purpose of the reports issued by the Citizens Budget Commission is to recommend how New York City, and beginning in 1984 New York State, could save money and better their financial situation. The reports include long-term and short-term studies. The size and complexity of New York City's budget has resulted in a need for continuous revision over the years. The first folder is undated, but due to its significance of listing some of the reports is housed first in the series. The remainder of the series is in chronological order. These reports document financial issues of concern from the 1930s to the 1990s.
  - List of Reports, Undated (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1931 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1933 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1934 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 4)
  - Reports, 1946 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1954 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1956 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1957 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1963 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1965 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 10)
  - Reports, 1966 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 11)
  - Reports, 1967 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 12)
  - Reports, 1968 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 13)
  - Reports, 1969 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 14)
  - Reports, 1969 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 15)
  - Reports, 1970 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 16)
  - Reports, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 17)
  - Reports, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 18)
  - Reports, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Reports), Folder 19)